(
"ai_sub_version": "3.6.0",
"generated_at": "2026-09-30T01:49:41.914247",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"service_tier": null,
"service_tier_subtitles": null,
"service_tier_lyrics": null,
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
パレ...
Parade...
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it shines bright!
呼び合う声を合図に
With our calling voices as the signal
パレ パレ パレ 探しに行く
Parade, parade, parade, off we go to search
スタートは何度だって
We can restart as many times as it takes
ただ 独り言 綴った
I simply scribbled down my inner monologues
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I just ran forward, longing for a start
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit up in the distant gloom
それは 眩しすぎた名前
Was a name that shone far too brightly
それは 優しすぎる思い出
Were memories that were all too tender
もっと 近付いて手を伸ばした
Drawing closer, I reached out my hand
思いがけず結び合った
Unexpectedly, our paths intertwined
ほら 今 迷子は僕らになった
Look, now the lost ones have become "us"
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it shines bright!
悔しさも愛おしさも 連れておいで
Bring along all the frustration and affection too
風 夢 羽 飛び立たせるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we'll make them take flight
ささやかな祈りは光
A humble prayer becomes light
終わりなき兆し
A sign of something endless
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Finding you is something I can be proud of
ここから これから アワ パレ パレ
From here on out, our parade, parade
まだ 頼りない予感を
Still holding onto an uncertain premonition
歌を 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
Singing out loud is nothing to be ashamed of
誰も 解けないイマジナリー
An imaginary world no one can unravel
いつか また会えるおまじない
A spell that ensures we will meet again someday
あの日 ゼロに始まったストーリー
A story that started from zero that day
数え切れない事のかな
Is it amidst countlessly many events?
数えるような思いじゃないさ
These feelings aren't something to be measured
ほら 今 僕らを ひとつと呼ぼう
Look, right now, let's call ourselves one!
パレ パレ パレ 美しいんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it's so beautiful!
許し合える切ない夜はきらめく
Painful nights of forgiving each other sparkle brightly
雨 晴れ カレ またとない空
Rain, shine, or change—an irreplaceable sky
ふさわしい旅路とは 君と歩くことさ
A journey truly fitting is one walked with you
君と歩くことなんだ
It's all about walking together with you
「ただいま」を聞けば
Whenever I hear "I'm home"
「おかえり」って叫ぶよ
I'll shout back "Welcome back!"
当たり前じゃないから
Because none of this is taken for granted
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it shines bright!
暗がりを満たすのは君だ 僕だ
Filling the darkness is you, and it's me
パレ パレ パレ 輝くんだよ
Parade, parade, parade, it shines bright!
悔しさも愛おしさも 連れておいで
Bring along all the frustration and affection too
風 夢 羽 飛び立たせるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we'll make them take flight
ささやかな祈りは光
A humble prayer becomes light
終わりなき兆し
A sign of something endless
君と飛び込んでいく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in together with you—it's a wonderful start
ここから これから アワ パレ パレ
From here on out, our parade, parade
アワ パレ パレ
Our parade, parade
ということで！
And so!
RosaMiA アコースティックライブ 始まりました！
The RosaMiA Acoustic Live has begun!
イエーイ！
Yay!
どうでしたか？
How was that?
1曲目からね
Starting right off with the first song...
『Our Parade』の？ なんかさ、こういう感じで
"Our Parade"? Singing this song in this kind of style...
この曲歌ったことなかったから
We've never performed it like this before, so...
ドキドキしちゃった。ドキドキしながら。
My heart was pounding! I was so nervous doing it.
分かる。3声になってましたね。
I know, right? We had a three-part harmony going on.
はい。なんか最後ポーズ決めるの忘れかけてたよね？
Yeah. And we almost forgot to make the final pose at the end, right?
集中しすぎて！ 歌に集中しすぎてちょっと焦ってたかも。
We were way too focused! Focused so much on singing that we panicked a bit.
あ、もうすでに... え？
Ah, already... Huh?
なんと...
What a surprise...
えー、こちら... ハッシュタグのトレンドで...
Um, right here... on the hashtag trends...
3位に入ってるらしい！
We're apparently ranked 3rd!
えー！すごい！ありがとうございます！
What?! Amazing! Thank you so much!
とりあえずちょっと自己紹介から...
For now, let's start with individual introductions.
じゃあ、ちょっと... よろしくお願いします。
Okay then, please go ahead.
では、自己紹介させていただきます。
Well then, I'll introduce myself.
RosaMIAの「ロー」担当、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです！アロハ～！
In charge of the "Ro" in RosaMIA, I'm Aki Rosenthal, also known as AkiRose! Aloha~!
アロハ～！そして...
Aloha~! And next...
はい！RosaMIAの「ミ」担当、長女の大神ミオです！よろしくお願いします！
Hi! In charge of the "Mi" in RosaMIA, the eldest sister, Ookami Mio! Pleased to meet you!
イエーイ！そして...
Yay! And...
はい！RosaMIAの「ア」担当、末っ子のAZKiです！よろしくお願いします！
Hi! In charge of the "A" in RosaMIA, the youngest sister, AZKi! Pleased to meet you!
板に付いてる！生き生きと末っ子言ってるよね。
You sound so natural calling yourself the youngest!
RosaMIAだとね、末っ子でいられる... 幸せです。ありがとうございます！
In RosaMIA, I get to be the youngest... I'm so happy. Thank you!
長女、長女...
Eldest sister, eldest sister...
長女、次女、末っ子で...
Eldest, second, and youngest sister...
三姉妹でやらせていただいております。
We're performing as three sisters.
はい、ということでね、この3人でRosaMIAというグループをやらせていただいているんですけども...
So the three of us form the group RosaMIA...
なんとですね、このRosaMIAでライブをするのは今回初めてということで！
And surprisingly, this is our very first live performance as RosaMIA!
初めて！
First time!
しかも、生歌唱のライブということでね、3人でいっぱい練習しましたね！
What's more, it's a live singing concert, so the three of us practiced a lot!
練習しましたー！合宿のように頑張ってね！部活みたいでさ、楽しかった！
We sure did! We worked hard like a training camp! It felt like an after-school club, so much fun!
そうだね！部活だったら合唱部みたいな感じだね！
That's right! Like a choir club!
たくさん練習した1曲目、どうでしたでしょうか？
We practiced a lot, so how was our first song?
どうでしたか？一番難しいまであるか？ / いや、そんなことはない！
How was it? Honestly, it might be our most difficult song! / No way!
そんなことはなかった、でもかなり難しい方ではあった。 / そうだね。
Well, maybe not, but it was definitely on the harder side. / Right.
パート分けでしたよね。 / そうだね、パート分けが難しかったかも。
Dividing the vocal parts was tough. / Yeah, allocating the parts was probably the hardest bit.
トレンドが3位に既に入っているという情報ですが...
Meanwhile, we heard that we're already #3 on trends, but...
はい！ハッシュタグはこちらとなっております！
Yes! Here is our official hashtag!
「#RosaMiAアコースティックライブ」というタグで、皆さんどしどしXでポストしてくださいね！
Please use "#RosaMiAアコースティックライブ" to post on X!
お願いします！後でエゴサするので！応援だったり感想とか...
Please do! We'll search for posts later! Give us your support and impressions...
分かる！呟いていっぱいね、盛り上げてくれたり...
I know! Tweet a lot and hype us up...
知らない人にも届けたいですよね！ / お願いします！
We want to reach people who don't know us yet too! / Yes please!
あ、今2位になってるよって！ / え！2位？！凄すぎる！
Oh, people are saying we're #2 now! / What?! #2?! That's amazing!
ありがとうございます！ぜひぜひいっぱいポストしてね！
Thank you so much! Please keep posting a lot!
というわけでですね... / はぁ～... どんどんいっちゃうんですかこれ？それとも永遠にここでトークしてるんですか？
So then... / Wow... Are we moving on quickly, or are we chatting here forever?
え、ちょっとさ... お水飲もうか！ちょっと一瞬のお水...
Huh, wait a sec... Let's grab some water! Just a quick water break...
一瞬お水飲ませてくださいね。
Please let us drink some water for a moment.
お水はおいしい。
Water tastes so good.
いや、「一瞬お水飲ませてください」とか言いつつ...
Even after saying "let us drink water for a moment"...
次は... もうそろそろ次の曲いっちゃいますか？いっちゃいます？
Next is... Should we move on to the next song soon? Shall we?
というわけで次の曲は、うちとアキちゃんの二人ということで！
So the next song will be performed by Aki-chan and me!
ここからは二人ずつ歌っていくんですね！ / そうなんですよ。
From here on, you'll be singing in pairs! / That's right.
じゃあ二人は準備お願いします！ / はい！AZKiちゃんにもね、お水飲んでもらったところ恐縮なんですけれども...
Alright then, please get ready! / Yes! Sorry to bother you right after you drank water, AZKi-chan...
MCをお願いして... / 2人が今準備しておりますので...
...to handle the MCing... / While the two of them prepare...
はーい！みんな、RosaMIAのアコースティックライブ来てくれてありがとう！1曲目いかがでしたか？
Hi~! Everyone, thank you for coming to RosaMIA's acoustic live! How was the first song?
『Our Bright Parade』。今回ね、ぜひアレンジにも注目していただきたいなと。
"Our Bright Parade". This time, I'd really love for you to pay attention to the arrangement.
ちょっといつもと違うおしゃれなアレンジになっておりますので。
It's turned into a stylish, slightly different arrangement than usual.
そこもね、それと合わせて3人のハーモニーを聴いていただけたらなと思っております。
I hope you can enjoy that along with our three-part harmony.
お、というところで2人が準備できたみたいなので...
Oh, looks like the two of them are ready now, so...
はい、出来ました！出来ました！
Yes, we're ready! We're ready!
いいですか？はい、聴いていただきましょう！『JANE DOE』。
Ready? Alright, please listen to "JANE DOE".
JANE DOE
まるでこの世界で 二人だけみたいだね
It's as if it's just the two of us in this world, isn't it?
なんて少しだけ 夢をみてしまっただけ
I was just dreaming a little dream, that's all.
つま先に月明かり 花束の香り 指に触れる指
Moonlight at my feet, the scent of a bouquet, fingers touching fingers.
さよなら もう行かなきゃ 何もかも...
Goodbye, I have to go now, leaving everything behind...
忘れて
Forget it
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on top of glass
痛むごとに 血が流れて 落ちていく
Every time it hurts, blood flows and drips down
お願い その赤い足跡を たどって
Please, follow those red footprints
会いに来て
And come to see me
錆びたプールに 放たれていく金魚
Goldfish released into a rusted pool
沓箱の中 隠した林檎
An apple hidden inside a shoe locker
血涙描く 君の肌に残る傷は
Tracing bloody tears, the wounds remaining on your skin...
蜂のように 迷い込んだ迷子
Like a bee wandering, a lost child in confusion
どこに どこにいるの
Where, where are you?
何をして 何を見ているの
What are you doing? What are you looking at?
この世を間違いで満たそう
Let us fill this world with mistakes
そばにいてよ 遊びに来よう
Stay by my side, come play with me
どこにいるの
Where are you?
ガラスの上を 裸足のまま歩く
Walking barefoot on top of glass
痛むごとに 血が流れて 落ちていく
Every time it hurts, blood flows and drips down
お願い その赤い足跡を たどって
Please, follow those red footprints
会いに来て
And come to see me
まるでこの世界で 2人だけみたいだね
It's almost as if we're the only two in this world, right?
なんて 少しだけ 夢を見てしまっただけ
Just... I was merely dreaming for a brief moment
はい！歌い切ったー！
Yes! We sang it all the way through!
いや、やっぱ素敵な曲だね
Yeah, it really is a wonderful song.
ホントだね。というわけで、アキちゃんとウチの JANE DOE でした！
It really is. So, that was Aki-chan and me performing JANE DOE!
めちゃくちゃ素敵！ありがとうー！
That was so wonderful! Thank you!
ちょっと緊張したー
I was a bit nervous~
そんなこと感じさせない歌声でしたよ
Your singing didn't show that at all!
本当に？すごかったー
Really? It was amazing~
この曲はこれから2人ずつ歌っていくんだろうなって思ってるかもしれないんですけど
You might be thinking that people will be singing this song in pairs from now on,
どこが難しかったですか？この曲は
What part was difficult for this song?
えー！でもやっぱハモりが原曲より少し多めにハモる場所を作ってて
Eh! Well, but the harmonies, we made slightly more harmony parts than in the original song,
確かに！そこの掛け合いとか合わせるのとか
Indeed! Syncing up those back-and-forths...
呼吸感とか？
like the breathing and timing?
でもアキちゃんが以前アキちゃんのライブでJANE DOEやってるからかわかんないけど
But maybe because Aki-chan did JANE DOE at her own live show before, I don't know,
ほぼ完璧だったわけ！
but she was almost perfect!
いやいや！そんなことないよ！
No no! That's not true!
最初から出来上がってて、練習しなきゃいけないのウチだったわけ！
She was ready right from the start, so I was the one who needed to practice!
アキロゼの生誕祭で、みよちゃんパートのメロディを歌わせてもらったことがあって
At AkiRosenthal's birthday festival, I got to sing the melody of Miyo-chan's part before,
で、こっちの米津さんパートは初挑戦だったんだけど
and this Kenshi Yonezu part was my first attempt,
分かってたから最初からほぼ完璧で！
but because she understood it, it was almost perfect right from the start!
そんなことないです！
That's really not the case!
ウチはあわわあわわってしてて、めちゃくちゃ素敵な声の伸びだったり
I was all flustered, but your vocal extension was so wonderful...
ハモれてすごい楽しかった！
Harmonizing with you was super fun!
かなりアキちゃんのハモりに助けられたというか
I was really saved by Aki-chan's harmony, or should I say...
やっぱハモり上手いからさ、アキちゃん！
After all, you're so good at harmonizing, Aki-chan!
天性のハモリスト！
A natural-born harmonist!
ハモり好きなんだよね！
You love harmonizing, right!
まだまだ精進させていただきますが、じゃあ…
I'll keep striving to improve, but well...
そろそろあれですかね？
Is it about time for that?
え！？もう行っちゃうの！？
Eh?! Are you leaving already?!
まだ引っ張って話すなら長々始めますけど(笑)
If we're gonna keep dragging this out to chat, I'll start rambling endlessly!
まぁそろそろね、次の準備ということで、みよちゃんとAZKiちゃんに歌ってもらうので
Well, it's about time to prepare for the next performance with Miyo-chan and AZKi-chan singing...
よいしょっと
Up we go.
頑張ろう あやちゃん 頑張ろうね
Let's do our best, Aya-chan. Let's do our best.
緊張するよ ちょっと 緊張するね
I'm getting nervous. - Me too.
ちょっとお水飲もうかな お水飲んでね
I think I'll drink some water. - Drink some water.
ふたりともお水飲んでもらって
Let's have both of them drink some water.
じゃあその間にアキロゼちょっとコメントをあれしようかな
In the meantime, AkiRoze will read some comments.
うんうんうん 草っていう文字がすごく黄緑で目立って拾いやすいなと思って
"Kusa" in bright green really stands out and is easy to spot.
うちの自作です
That's our custom one.
あ、そうなの？可愛いスタンプ！
Oh, really? What a cute stamp!
やーでもね こうやってみんなも「待ってたよ」とか「RosaMiAのライブ嬉しい」って声を見てたので
But really, I saw everyone saying "We were waiting!" and "So happy for RosaMiA's live!"
すごいありがとうございます ちょっと緊張して初挑戦なのでね 色々と頑張るっていうことでやってますので 応援よろしくお願いします
Thank you so much. We're nervous as it's our first attempt, but we'll do our best, so please support us.
では2人は準備できたみたいなので 次の曲聴いていただきましょう
Now then, it looks like those two are ready, so let's listen to the next song.
『夜光通信』
"Yakou Tsuushin"
聞こえますか
Can you hear me?
ハロー ハロー 聞こえますか
Hello, hello, can you hear me?
そっちは何年？
What year is it over there?
正しく分かり合う手段は
The ways to truly understand each other...
ひとつじゃないさ
...aren't just one.
漂う時間はどこへ行くのか
Where does this drifting time go?
サヨナラはいつ誰が決めるの
Who decides when to say goodbye, and when?
その手に触れようと願ってる
Wishing to touch those hands...
本当さ
...it's true.
トワの夜光
Eternal night light,
君に歌う
singing for you.
世界中が君に意地悪でも
Even if the whole world is mean to you,
思い出して
remember,
覚えていて
hold onto it.
まぶたの裏
Behind your eyelids,
ずっとまた会えるからね
we can always meet again.
穏やかに
Gently,
健やかに
peacefully,
奏でる風景
in this playing scenery.
君だって私だって
Both you and I,
消えるのは
what disappears...
言葉だけ
...is only words.
ふわり君を抱きしめてあげるからね
I'll softly hold you tight,
泣かないで
so please don't cry.
延々と続く今日は
Today, endlessly continuing,
拝啓のようで
feels like a greeting.
突然の幸せまでも
Even sudden happiness...
くらませるんだ
...gets dazzled away.
忘れないで
Don't forget,
どこでだってつながる回線
a line that connects wherever you are.
寂しい宇宙とオレンジの公園
A lonely universe and an orange park.
親しい心の限りを
With all of my close heart,
歌おう
let's sing.
トワの夜光
Eternal night light,
届くよね
it reaches you, right?
幻想よりも優しい形のまま
Remaining in a form gentler than fantasy.
濡れそぼる
Wet and drenched,
その頬を
those cheeks,
こっそり撫でて乾かしてあげるからね
I'll secretly stroke and dry them for you.
何度だって
Again and again.
トワの夜光
Eternal night light,
虚空に歌う
singing into the void.
会いたいよ 消えたくなんてないよ
I want to see you, I don't want to disappear.
思い出して
Remember,
覚えていて
hold onto it,
今ここで笑い合ったことを
how we laughed together right here, right now.
トワの夜光
Eternal night light,
君に歌う
singing for you.
世界中が君に意地悪でも
Even if the whole world is mean to you,
思い出して
remember,
覚えていて
hold onto it.
まぶたの裏
Behind your eyelids,
ずっとまた会えるからね
we can always meet again.
サヨナラは
As for goodbyes,
as for goodbyes,
ねぇ 誰が決めるもの？
hey, who is to decide them?
消えるのは言葉...
What disappears are words...
ふわり君を抱きしめてあげるからね
I'll softly wrap my arms around you,
泣かないで
so don't cry.
というわけで「夜光通信」歌わせていただきました！
And with that, we just performed "Yakou Tsuushin"!
「夜光通信」！ありがとうございます！
"Yakou Tsuushin"! Thank you so much!
いやぁ、すごくね、素敵で聞き入ってたんですけど
Wow, that was so wonderful, I was completely spellbound listening...
あの、なんと嬉しいお知らせが入っていまして
But listen, we actually have some great news!
何ですか？何ですか？
What is it? What is it?
トレンド1位を！こちら！ハッシュタグでいただきました！
We reached #1 on trending with our hashtag right here!
やったー！ありがとうございます！みんなのおかげ！
Yay! Thank you so much! It's all thanks to everyone!
みんなのおかげ！RosaMiAの名を轟かせて！
Thanks to everyone! Spreading the name of RosaMiA far and wide!
嬉しいね！1位なんてすごい！ありがとう、みんな！
So happy! #1 is amazing! Thank you, everyone!
コメントでも「アコースティックバージョンすごくいい」っていうのがたくさんあったし
There were so many comments saying the acoustic version is so good!
やっぱりハーモニーがすごく綺麗って、みんな言ってくれてて
And everyone was saying how beautiful the harmony was!
嬉しいな！上手く出来たよね！出来た出来た！
I'm so happy! It turned out great, right? Yes, it did!
向かい合って歌ってるところとか、ぞくぞくしたもんね
Singing face-to-face like that gave me goosebumps!
実はですね、こちら選曲はAZKiちゃんがしてくれまして
Actually, AZKi-chan picked this song for us!
はい、私！
Yes, I did!
今回はミオちゃんの枠でやらせていただくこともあり、僭越ながら... 大好きすぎて、ミオちゃんの「夜光通信」を歌いまくっててすみません！
Since we're hosting on Mio-chan's stream, I love this song so much that I've been singing Mio-chan's "Yakou Tsuushin" non-stop, sorry!
いやいや、嬉しいんですけどね。本人よりも歌ってるという噂がある（笑）
No, no, I'm super happy! Rumor has it you sing it more than I do!
「あれ？AZKiちゃん今日も歌ってる！」って（笑）
People are like, "Huh? AZKi-chan is singing it again today!"
めっちゃ嬉しいんだけどね、本当に！ありがとうございます！
But I'm honestly super happy about it! Thank you so much!
かなり今回アコースティックアレンジで、より曲の良さも伝わったんじゃないかな
With this acoustic arrangement, I think the beauty of the song really shone through even more.
エモさがね！より強調されてたよね！歌詞も素敵ですし。
The emotional vibe was highlighted so well! The lyrics are wonderful, too.
よかった～本当に！聞き入りました。
It was really great! I was completely engrossed.
よかったー！みんなよかったかな？感想お願いします！
So glad! Did everyone enjoy it? Please leave your thoughts!
お願いします！
Please do!
じゃあ、というわけで！
All right then, with that said...
ここで二人出てきたということは、AZKiちゃんとアキちゃんの二人で... バトンなんじゃないですか？
Since the two of you came out, does that mean it's time to pass the baton to AZKi-chan and Aki-chan?
やります！ちょっとお水飲もう。この間にうちMCやるからさ。
That's right! Let's grab some water. I'll cover the MC while you do!
はい、ということで！大神ミオチャンネルの大神ミオです！よろしくお願いします！
All right then! I'm Ookami Mio from the Ookami Mio Channel! Nice to meet you all!
こんばんみぉーん！うちだよ！大神ミオだよ～！
Good evening-mioon! It's me! Ookami Mio~!
ミオかわいい！ありがとう！助かる～！
Mio, you're cute! Thank you! That helps a lot~!
あんまり休憩してないんだよな（笑）チャチャ入れてんだよな。
I haven't really been resting much, just interjecting with comments!
はい、というわけでね、皆さんコメントいっぱいありがとうございます！
Anyway, thank you all so much for all the comments!
RosaMiAアコースティックライブでね、トレンド1位にもしていただいたということで、タグも賑わっていることでしょう！後で感想見るのめっちゃ楽しみにしてます！
Thanks to you all, #RosaMiA Acoustic Live hit #1 on trending! I'm sure the hashtag is hopping, and I can't wait to check your feedback later!
というわけで、準備もよさそうなので...
Looks like they're ready to go now...
そろそろ聴いていただきましょうか、皆さん。
Shall we listen to the next song, everyone?
では、皆さんの準備はいいですか？
Now then, is everyone ready?
聴いていただきましょう。「月のワルツ」
Please listen to "Tsuki no Waltz" (Waltz of the Moon).
ん... ん...
Mm... Mm...
はぁ... はぁ...
Ah... Ah...
こんなに月が青い夜は
On a night when the moon is this blue,
不思議なことが起きるよ
mysterious things happen.
どこか深い森の中で
Somewhere deep inside the forest,
彷徨う私
I wander lost.
立ち込める霧の先が開けて
Beyond the thick fog, the space opens up,
ワイン色のテーブルウェア
revealing wine-colored tableware.
真っ赤なキノコの傘の下で
Under the cap of a bright red mushroom,
踊りが始まる
a dance begins.
どこにいるの
Where are you?
時間の国の迷子
A lost child in the land of time.
帰り道がわからないの
I don't know the way back home.
待って待っているのに
Even though I wait and wait for you.
眠れるこの魂は あなたを探し森の中
This sleeping soul searches for you in the forest.
チャンドラ・マハルの王子様が 膝まずいてワルツに誘う
The prince of Chandra Mahal kneels and invites me to a waltz.
まつげの長い蝶たちが
Butterflies with long eyelashes
シフォンのドレスでひらひらと
flutter around in chiffon dresses.
虹色のタイツのカブトムシは 剣のダンス
Beetles in rainbow tights perform a sword dance.
求めるものはなに？
What is it that you seek?
惑わしのラビリンス ミルク色の霧の彼方
A labyrinth of enchantment beyond the milky fog.
確かな愛がほしい
I want a love that is certain.
冷たいこのつま先を 白鳥の羽でくるんで
Wrap these cold toes in swan feathers.
チャンドラ・マハルの王子様は あなたに似た瞳で笑う
The prince of Chandra Mahal smiles with eyes that resemble yours.
満ちては欠ける
Waxing and waning,
空を行く 神秘の船
a mysterious ship travels across the sky.
変わらないものなどないと 語りかけてくる
It speaks to me, saying that nothing stays unchanged.
こんなに月が青い夜は 不思議なことが起きるよ
On a night when the moon is so blue, strange things happen.
どこか見知らぬ森の中で さ迷う私
Wandering alone in an unfamiliar forest.
こんなに月が青い夜は 不思議なことが起きるよ
On a night when the moon is so blue, strange things happen.
愛することは信じること いつかその胸に抱かれ 眠る夢を見る
To love is to believe; I dream of sleeping held in your arms.
はい
All right!
ということで『月のワルツ』でした
And with that, that was "Tsuki no Waltz"!
すごいよかったよ！
That was so good!
素晴らしかった！
That was wonderful!
大変だったー！
That was tough!
いや、あのさ、うちはさ
Well, you know, for me...
最初から2人が練習してるときから知ってるんだけど
I've known since the beginning when you two were practicing,
今日、完成した感ない？
but doesn't it feel like it reached completion today?
え、本当に！？
Wait, really?!
えー、嬉しい！
Aw, I'm so happy!
あるよ！本当に！
It really does! Truly!
すごく上手くなった！
You got so much better!
えー、嬉しい！やったー！
Yay, I'm so happy! We did it!
綺麗だったー
It was so beautiful.
いやー、でもさ
Man, but still...
緊張したよね。ハモリでさ、入るところがいつもドキドキして
We were nervous. The parts where we enter with harmony always make my heart race.
今回そう、アキちゃんメインでAZKiがね、ハモリで入らせてもらっているんですけれど
Yeah, Aki-chan was main vocals while AZKi came in with harmonies,
このハモリが...
and those harmonies...
だから練習した...すごく
That's why we practiced so much!
いや、めっちゃ練習したもんね
Yeah, you guys practiced like crazy!
確かに！
Definitely!
いや、本当偉いなって、なんか感動しちゃった
Honestly, you did so well. I was really moved.
成長したよ、やっぱり
You've really grown!
素晴らしいなって
It was wonderful.
いいハモリでしたね
That was such a great harmony.
ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much!
本当にね
Really, though.
でもここで満足しちゃいけませんよ
But we can't be satisfied with just this!
ここで満足しちゃ...だってまだ3人でさ
Satisfied already? But the three of us...
1曲しか歌ってないから！
have only sung one song so far!
確かに！
That's true!
ROSaMiAなのに！
Even though we're ROSaMiA!
そうだよ！ここからね！
That's right! From here on!
みんなもまだまだ...
Everyone, there's still much more to come...
何言ってた？
What were you saying?
次何でしょう？何だろうね。
What's next? I wonder what it is.
でも本当にね、ステージも綺麗でね
But really, the stage is so pretty too.
さっき何か残ってませんでした？
Wasn't there something left on stage earlier?
あ、今なくなっちゃったけど…
Ah, it's gone now, but...
でもコメントで「今日も月が綺麗ですね」って言ってくれてたから
But people in the comments were saying "The moon is pretty today too."
『月のワルツ』のイメージでね
With the image of "Tsuki no Waltz"...
そうなんです。月のカフェに乗らせてもらいまして。
That's right. We got to ride on the moon cafe.
ここはなんか宇宙空間なのですかね？
Is this like outer space?
宇宙空間？すごいステージだ。綺麗だな。
Outer space? What an amazing stage. It's so beautiful.
じゃあ、ちょっとね、そろそろ次の曲に行っちゃいます？
Well then, shall we move on to the next song soon?
行っちゃう？
Shall we?
やばい、緊張してお水飲みたいかも。
Oh no, I'm nervous, I might want to drink water.
お水飲みタイム。緊張してきた。
Water drinking time. I'm getting nervous.
緊張してきた。大丈夫かな。
I'm getting nervous. Will I be okay?
いや、次の曲も結構ね、気合いがいるよね。
Yeah, the next song takes quite a lot of energy too, right?
気合いを入れまして…
Getting ourselves pumped up...
入ります。気合い入れます。
Here we go. Getting pumped up.
おっ、なんとステージがちょっと変わりまして…
Oh, look, the stage changed a bit...
このキューブはなんかちょっと懐かしくないですか？見覚えが…
Doesn't this cube feel a bit nostalgic? Looks familiar...
実はアキロゼの生誕祭で2人に来てもらって
Actually, for AkiRosel's birthday stream when I invited you two...
最初に3人で歌わせてもらった時に
When the three of us sang together for the first time,
こういうキューブ状のステージで歌わせてもらったんだけど
we sang on a cube-shaped stage like this.
それをちょっと彷彿とさせるというか、再現していただいて
It feels reminiscent of that, like they recreated it for us.
『君の銀の庭』を歌ったという記憶があります。
I remember we sang "Kimi no Gin no Niwa".
え、それ歌うんですか？
Eh, are we singing that?
そんな、ねえ。そんな思い出もありますけれど。
No, no. We do have those memories, though.
実はね、まだ聴いてない人はよかったら聴いてみてください。
Actually, if you haven't listened to it yet, please check it out.
あ、そうですね。アキロゼのチャンネルで上がってますね。
Ah, right. It's uploaded on AkiRosel's channel.
そうなんです。というわけで…
That's right. So...
ここからなんと…
From here, surprisingly...
2曲連続で歌っていきます。
we will sing two songs in a row.
ちょっと音を合わせさせてください。難しい曲なので。
Please let us tune for a bit. It's a difficult song.
いきなり歌から始まりますからね。
Because it starts right away with singing.
Every day I listen to my heart
ひとりじゃない
I am not alone
深い胸の奥で つながってる
Deep within my heart, we are connected
果てしない時を越えて 輝く
Shining across endless time
星が
The stars...
出会えた奇跡 教えくれて
teach me the miracle of us meeting
Every day I listen to my heart
ひとりじゃない
I am not alone
この空のもと 胸に
Under this sky, held close...
抱かれて
to the heart
Jupiter
[Song: Jupiter]
私のこの両手で 何ができるの？
What can I do with these two hands of mine?
痛みに触れさせて じっと目を閉じて
Let me touch the pain, gently closing my eyes
夢を失うよりも 悲しいことは
Something sadder than losing a dream
自分を信じてあげられないこと
is not being able to believe in yourself
愛を学ぶために 孤独があるなら
If solitude exists so that we may learn love,
意味のないことなど…
then nothing is without meaning...
Every day I listen to my heart
ひとりじゃない
I am not alone.
心根のしじまに
In the silence of my heart,
耳をすまして
I listen closely.
私を呼んだなら
If you call for me,
どこへでも行くわ
I will go anywhere.
あなたのその涙
I will make those tears of yours
私のものに
my very own.
いまは自分を
Right now,
抱きしめて
embrace yourself.
命のぬくもり感じて
Feel the warmth of life.
私たちは誰も
None of us
ひとりじゃない
are ever alone.
ありのままでずっと愛されている
We are forever loved, just as we are.
望むように生きて輝く未来を
Living as you wish towards a shining future,
いつまでも歌うわ あなたのために
I will sing forever for you.
私に何ができる？
What can I do?
記憶をたどり
Traced back through memories,
優しさと夢の源
to the source of gentleness and dreams.
愛の星に導かれ
Guided by the star of love,
生まれるために
to be born into this world.
魂のルフラン
Soul's Refrain
時の中で静かに震えている
Trembling quietly within time,
命の行方を問いかけるように
as if asking where life is headed.
指先は私を求める
Your fingertips reach out for me.
抱きしめていた運命のあなたは
You, the destiny I held in my arms,
季節に咲くまるで儚い花
are like a fleeting flower blooming in season.
希望の匂いを胸に残して
Leaving the scent of hope inside my heart.
な姿で
In a vivid figure...
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
生まれる前に
before your birth,
あなたが過ごした 大地へと
back to the earth where you once lived.
この腕に還りなさい
Return into my arms,
めぐり逢うため
in order to meet again.
奇跡は起こるよ 何度でも
Miracles will happen, time after time.
魂のルフラン
It's the soul's refrain.
祈るように まぶた閉じたときに
When I close my eyes as if praying,
世界はただ闇の底に消える
the world simply vanishes into the depths of darkness.
それでも鼓動はまた動きだす
Even so, my heartbeat starts moving again,
限りある永遠を探して
searching for a limited eternity.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
記憶をたどり
tracing your memory,
優しさと夢の水源へ
back to the source of gentleness and dreams.
あなたも還りなさい
You too must return,
愛しあうため
in order to love each other.
心も体もくりかえす
Mind and body repeat again and again.
魂のルフラン
It's the soul's refrain.
私に還りなさい
Return to me,
生まれる前に
before your birth,
あなたが過ごした 大地へと
back to the earth where you once lived.
この腕に還りなさい
Return into my arms,
めぐり逢うため
in order to meet again.
奇跡は起こるよ 何度でも
Miracles will happen, time after time.
魂のルフラン
It's the soul's refrain.
ということで
And so...
はい！ 2曲連続で聴いていただきました！
Yes! You just heard two songs in a row!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
わかってるよ... わかってる、わかってるよ... 自分がいちばんわかってるよね！
I know, I know... I know! I know better than anyone!
一瞬振り返ったら、このままなんか安心しちゃった...
When I turned around for a second, I kind of felt relieved...
ちょっとヤバい、これアキちゃんもしかして忘れてるかもと思って、1小節目歌おうかなと思って一瞬迷ったんだけど、でも...
I thought, "Oh no, maybe Aki-chan forgot," and hesitated for a moment wondering if I should sing the first measure, but...
すみません！
I'm sorry!
でも途中から気づいたから！ 気づいたからよかった！
But you noticed halfway through! I'm glad you noticed!
はい、ギリギリ。せーの... セーフ！
Yep, barely in time. Ready, set... Safe!
セーフ、セーフ、セーフ！
Safe, safe, safe!
もう1回やったっていいんじゃない？
Couldn't we do it one more time?
ヤバい！ もう1回やったらヤバい！
Oh no! Doing it again would be bad!
リテイクはヤバい！
A retake would be terrible!
まあでもね、みなさんすごくコメントの勢いがね、物語ってますよ！
Well, everyone's comment speed really speaks volumes!
「すごくかっこよかったよ」って言ってくれてるよ！
They're saying "That was so cool!"
ありがとう！ これが生（ライブ）の証明ですから！
Thank you! This is proof that it's live!
確かに！ 身を切って証明した！
True! Sacrificed myself to prove it!
完全体はいつか！ 成長コンテンツだからさ！
Our perfect form will come someday! It's growth content, after all!
一度もこの失敗さ、今までの練習でも一度もなかったのに！ どうしたの？！
We never made this mistake once in practice up until now! What happened?!
怖ーい！ こんなことなかったのに！ 本番の魔物が来たね！
Scary! It never happened before! The live performance demon showed up!
本番の魔物が... 安心しちゃった後ろ姿見たら...
The live performance demon... Looking at your backs made me feel too relieved...
「あれ？」って、全員、全員後ろ向いてる？！
"Huh?" Everyone, everyone's facing backward?!
「あ、アキちゃん...」みたいな。 恥ずかしくて火が出るかと...
Like, "Ah, Aki-chan..." I felt so embarrassed I thought I'd burst into flames...
でもね、なんとかね、ここまでいっぱいに練習した曲をお披露目できて嬉しいなって思ってるんですけれどもの！
But still, we're so glad we could showcase the songs we practiced so hard for!
ここでですね、うちから...
And now, from me...
ちょっとね、お知らせというか、みんな知ってるんですけど...
A little announcement, or rather, everyone already knows, but...
なんと！ 大神ミオ 誕生日記念グッズ、発売中でございます！
Ookami Mio Birthday Commemorative Goods are now on sale!
どーん！ お知らせ！ こちらチェックしてみてください！
Ta-da! Announcement! Please check this out!
スカジャンとですね、こちらアクリルキーホルダーとなっております！
It includes a Souvenir Jacket and an acrylic keychain!
こちらです！ こちら受注期間あと4日なので...
Here it is! The pre-order period has 4 days left, so...
急げ急げー！
Hurry, hurry!
もあるんです
There's also that!
はい、あのもしね買ってなくて、「あ、買い忘れてた」って人はね、あのちょっと早めに買っていただけるとっていうところではございます。
So, if you haven't bought it yet and realized, "Oh, I forgot to buy it!", please consider getting it as soon as possible.
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you for your support!
はい。というわけで、まあサラッとね、お知らせしちゃったんですけど...
All right. So, we briefly went over those announcements...
もう1個ありますよね？
But there's another one, right?
サムネイルに「告知あり」って...
The thumbnail said "Announcement Inside"...
そう、確かありましたけど...今日は3人の告知が！
That's right! Today, we have an announcement from all three of us!
なんですか？なんですか？
What is it? What could it be?
いいですか、言っちゃって？
Can I go ahead and say it?
言っちゃって！
Say it!
なんと...RosaMiAのファーストシングルが、デジタルリリースされます！
RosaMiA's first single will be released digitally!
タイトル、「Blossom Sinfonia」でございます！
The title is "Blossom Sinfonia"!
オリジナル楽曲ですね！3人のオリジナル楽曲なんですよ！
It's an original song! An original song by the three of us!
我らのRosaMiAのファーストシングルということで、ま、初めにふさわしいような、3人の声が咲き誇るような楽曲に、そして我らのRosaMiAロードも咲き誇ってくれるように、そんな華やかな1曲目となっております。
As RosaMiA's first single, it's a fitting start where our three voices come into full bloom. It's a gorgeous first song, hoping that our RosaMiA road will bloom just as brightly.
大事に育てていきたいなと思ってる曲ですし、みんなにも愛される曲になっていってくれたらいいなと思っておりますので、ぜひ...
It's a song we want to cherish and nurture, and we hope it becomes a song loved by everyone, so please...
この後24時から、各配信サイトでダウンロードできますので、ぜひぜひ聴いてくださいね！
Starting tonight at 24:00, it'll be available on various streaming sites, so please check it out!
お願いしまーす！
Please check it out!
というわけで...
And so...
でもこの曲どんな曲か気になる...
But I bet you're wondering what kind of song it is...
どんな曲なんだろう？華やか？
What kind of song is it? Is it gorgeous?
みんな聴きたいよね？みんなのコメントを読んでいます。
You all want to hear it, right? I'm reading everyone's comments.
その間に水飲もうよ。ビジュアルいい！ありがとう！
Let's drink some water in the meantime. "The visual looks great!" Thank you!
気になる！マジで！聴く！
"Curious!" "Seriously!" "I'll listen!"
ホロどり来るか？あ、あの...ホロどりさんどうですか？
Is Holodori coming? Um, how about Holodori?
どうなんですか、ホロどりさん？あきちゃん、可愛い水飲んできてね。
What about Holodori? Aki-chan, go drink some water, so cute.
気になるよねー？
You're curious, right?
ということでね、なんとアズちゃん、この後...
And so, Azu-chan, right after this...
お披露目しちゃうかもしれないって話。
We might just unveil it to everyone.
これは最後まで見逃せないってこと？
You mean we can't miss a single second until the end?
というわけでですね、なんとこの後、生歌唱にて初お披露目させていただきます！
That's right! Right after this, we'll perform it live for the very first time!
ハードル高くなってる！心を落ち着けて...
You're raising the bar! Calm down...
みんなに1回説明しておきたいんですけど、この曲、歌唱難易度がバチ高くくてですね...
I want to explain to everyone first, this song has an insanely high difficulty level...
今まで歌ってきた歌の中で一番の最難関歌となっております。
It's by far the most difficult song we've ever sung so far.
この曲一番最初に練習し始めたもんね。どの曲よりも一番練習したけど、それでもなお難しい！
We started practicing this song first, right? We practiced it more than any other song, but it's still so tough!
本当に難しい。これから聴いてもらうけどさ...
It really is difficult. You're about to hear it, but...
これを聴いてね、濃いハーモニーとか好きな人もいると思うから、「どうやって歌ってるんだろう」みたいな...
Some people love rich harmonies, so listening to it, you might wonder how we're singing it...
考察じゃないけど、聴いていただけたら嬉しいです。待ってます！
If you could listen and analyze those details, we'd be so happy. We're waiting!
じゃあ、本日24時からデジタルリリースされる曲となります。
Alright, this song will be digitally released tonight at midnight.
もういいですか、言っちゃって？ちょっと順番があるでしょ。
Can we start now? Hold on, there's a set order.
大丈夫？アキロゼは大丈夫じゃないよ、ちょっと緊張してる...
Are you okay? AkiRose isn't okay, she's a bit nervous...
大丈夫だよ！大丈夫、心配しないでね。練習の成果を発揮すればええねん。
You'll be fine! Don't worry. Just show the results of our practice.
というわけで...行きますよ。それじゃあ聴いてください。せーの！
All right... Here we go. Please listen. Ready, set...
Blossom Sinfonia！
Blossom Sinfonia!
遠くのあなたに 歌届くように
So that my song reaches you far away
宵におびえる 私がいる
Here I am, frightened by the nightfall
それでも明日に 期待している
Yet still looking forward to tomorrow
あの日に見つけた 奇跡の種
The seed of miracles we found on that day
いつでも そこには 希望がある
Whenever, hope is always there.
暗くても 一筋差す
Even in darkness, a single ray shines through.
明日への 光へと 手を伸ばしてる 今でも
Reaching out toward the light of tomorrow, even now.
途切れないように つないできたから
Because we've stayed connected so it won't break,
今 芽吹き始めた 未来があるの
there is a future that has begun to sprout now.
遠くのあなたに 歌届くように
So that our song reaches you in the distance,
この先も 紡ぐの
we will keep weaving it from here on out.
Ah...
大事に抱えた 希望の芽は
The sprout of hope we cherished tightly...
可憐で 儚い それでもいい
...is delicate and fleeting, but that's okay.
いつの日か 小さくても
Someday, even if it's small,
重なれば 鮮やかに 染め上げられる 世界を
when brought together, it can vividly color the world.
信じた未来へ 歩んできたから
Because we've walked toward the future we believed in,
今 手を取り合える 仲間がいるの
now we have companions whose hands we can hold.
遠くのあなたの 手を握れるように
So that we can hold your hand in the distance,
花は今 咲き誇る
the flowers are now in full bloom.
不安でも 大丈夫と
Even if anxious, saying "it's okay,"
くじけても 続けてきた
even if crushed, we kept going.
弱くてもいい 怖くてもいい
It's okay to be weak, it's okay to be scared.
咲かせると決めたの 行き渡れ あなたへ
We decided to make it bloom, spreading to you.
途切れないように つないできたから
Because we've stayed connected so it won't break,
今 鮮やかなほど 咲き誇る花
now, flowers bloom so vividly,
遠くのあなたに 歌届くように
so that our song reaches you in the distance.
変わらないよ ずっと 何があっても ずっと あなたへと 紡ぐの
It will never change, forever. No matter what happens, forever, we will weave it to you.
本日24時よりデジタルリリース！
Digital release starts at 24:00 today!
ぜひみんなRosaMiAの1stシングル聴いてね！
Be sure to listen to RosaMiA's 1st single, everyone!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
頑張った！頑張った！
We did our best! We did our best!
告知あり
[Announcement]